<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 15:54:00 -0300</pubDate><title><![CDATA[CLIENTS]]></title><url><![CDATA[clientes_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[			&lt;div id=&quot;homebanner&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;h1&gt;Clients&lt;/h1&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div id=&quot;barraceleste&quot;&gt;
						&lt;div class=&quot;contenedor&quot;&gt;
							Efficiency and commitment in the performance of each task
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div id=&quot;hometextos&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;In the last years, the main activity of the cooperative has been related to hydrocarbons like gas oil, fuel oil and gasoline, and the cooperative has provided services in order to:
:&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Facilitate liquid fuel storage to guarantee that industries will be able to work in case of a lack of fuel provision from other sources. &lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Provide the logistics necessary for hydrocarbon commercialization.&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Act as a port terminal in export and import operations.&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Supply power plants with liquid fuel.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;contenedor&quot;&gt;DUE TO THIS KIND OF SERVICES, THE COOPERATIVE HANDLES A CLIENT PORTFOLIO THAT INCLUDES SOME OF THE MAIN COMPANIES IN THE POWER SECTOR. &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1 relativo&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
						&lt;div class=&quot;contenedor imagenes3&quot;&gt;
							&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s01&quot; &gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;a01&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;a02&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;a03&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;a04&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;a05&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s02&quot; &gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;b01&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;b02&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;b03&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;b04&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s03&quot; &gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;c01&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;c02&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;c03&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;c04&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;div id=&quot;c05&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;div class=&quot;sombra2&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;h1&gt;PROVISION TO THE POWER SYSTEM&lt;/h1&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;In the last years, as a consequence of the sustained growth of the economic activity, the consumption of electric power has significantly risen, and more than 60 % of the electric power is produced in power plants run by fuels from mineral origin.&lt;/ br&gt;
The activities carried out by cooperative Decosur contribute to supply these power plants distributed along the whole country with fuel. While performing its activities Decosur has achieved an efficiency level appreciated by the bodies in charge of the electric power supply, and has also been awarded distinctions by the Secretaría de Energía de la Nación [Argentine Department of Energy].&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;We are proud of this responsibility not only because it made the cooperative growing in the last years until it doubled the number of workers and the premises´ capacity, but also, and more important, because it allows the cooperative to contribute to the country´s development. &lt;/p&gt;]]></content><author><![CDATA[admin]]></author><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
