<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 14:34:36 -0300</pubDate><title><![CDATA[COOPERATIVE]]></title><url><![CDATA[cooperativa_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[		&lt;div id=&quot;homebanner&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;h1&gt;Cooperative&lt;/h1&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1 relativo&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;imagen&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div id=&quot;barraceleste&quot;&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div id=&quot;hometextos&quot;&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Technicians, machinists, and administrative workers are part of the cooperative DECOSUR, and they all work under the principle that &lt;b&gt;commitment and responsibility&lt;/b&gt; constitute the foundation of the challenging activity they have been performing for many years. Together they satisfy the most demanding requirements in terms of operations´ efficiency and quality, and strive to continuously improve the processes developed to render the cooperative services.&lt;br /&gt;
Most of the cooperative current members worked for the firm Victorio De Bernardi S.A. [a corporation] and they put &lt;b&gt;the valuable experience gained there into work in the cooperative&lt;/b&gt;. However, the chief strength of our organization lies in the fact that the workers strongly committed themselves when they decided to take control of the bankrupt corporation themselves and turned it into a cooperative (that is to say, when they “recovered” the company). Thus, the main values of the cooperative are the responsibility, creativity, willingness to work, and participation of each worker-owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;icono_obreros&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;contenedor&quot;&gt;Responsibility, creativity, Willingness to work and participation of each worker-owner.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;sombra1 relativo&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;contenedor imagenes3&quot;&gt;
					&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s01&quot; &gt;&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s02&quot; &gt;&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;div class=&quot;imagen s03&quot; &gt;&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The cooperative is governed by its Estatuto Social [the cooperative´s bylaw] and its Reglamento Interno [the cooperative´s rules and regulations] approved by INAES [an Argentine institute in charge of promoting the creation of cooperatives] in accordance with the Ley Nacional de Cooperativas [Argentine act on cooperatives] and other regulations enacted by INAES. All the aforementioned rules have been enforced to organize the activities developed by the cooperative while guaranteeing that these activities are carried out in accordance with safety regulations as well as regulations to preserve the environment.

&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;


]]></content><author><![CDATA[admin]]></author><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
